АЛЕКСАНДР СВЕТЛИЧНЫЙ

Moscow, Russia ∘ asvetly1337@gmail.com ∘ +79281630500



PROFILE

I'm experienced full-stack developer with frontend as a major specialisation. At the moment I am mostly interested in developing frontend architectures and infrastructures. Besides development, I'm also passionate about managing teams, leading them in order to achieve unachievable. For me, a team is an living organism and infinite field for investigation.

EDUCATION

MM AT MSU, HIGH SCHOOL OF BUSINESS

DEVELOPING BUSINESS-MODEL FOR A CLOTHING COMPANY SEP 2018 - AUG 2020

MCS AT SFEDU, INSTITUTE OF MECHANICS, MATHEMATICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

STUDY OF THE THEORY OF "SIX HANDSHAKES" BASED ON THE SOCIAL GRAPH OF THE VKONTAKTE NETWORK SEP 2013 - AUG 2017

BIT AT SFEDU, INSTITUTE OF MECHANICS, MATHEMATICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

NAVIGATING AN AUTONOMOUS ROBOTIC SYSTEM ON A KNOWN MAP BASED ON ROS AND LEGO NXT SEP 2013 - AUG 2017

EXPERIENCE

SBERBANK OCT 2018 – PRESENT

FULL STACK DEVELOPER TYPESCRIPT · REACT · JAVA · SPRING · SPRING BOOT · JENKINS

Platform and services for monitoring corporate clients.

- member of the platform core-team;
- active inner-source contributor;
- developed a bunch of infrastructure things, ex. logger, cdn, csi, monorepository, pipeline for managing and publishing core modules, etc.

AUG 2017 – AUG 2018

WEB DEVELOPER RUBY ON RAILS · JAVASCRIPT · REACT · REDUX

Crowdfunding web-platform projectsforgood.com.

- worked with distributed, multicultural and multilanguage team;
- web messenger;
- website-wide and email notifications.

OCT 2016 – JUN 2017
WEB DEVELOPER
RUBY ON RAILS · JAVASCRIPT

Contributed to several projects, the most major ones are:

- chado.pro rails application with backbone.js (developed mobile version)
- fueled.com mixed app, contains of a static part with ruby and middleman and a blog part with django/wordpress.

PROGRESSIVE TECHNOLOGY OF SERVICE

APR 2016 – SEP 2016

RUBY ON RAILS · JAVASCRIPT

Platform for analysing statistics (project closed).

data visualisation;

WEB DEVELOPER

- authorization system with role management.